Heat.
Heat. Heat. N.
Hey,
Good morning and welcome to Movement
Church. Are you ready to worship the
Lord this morning?
All right, come on. Put your hands
together. Who's got joy in this place?
>> All right, here we go.
[music]
[music] There's a song in my spirit.
There's a joy in my soul. What a way
[singing]
I'll worship [music] anyway.
Only the devil [music and singing] can
try it. Try to quiet this song, but I'll
sing out even louder [singing and music]
than before.
I'm going to [music and singing] lift my
voice and sing. I'm going to give him
everything. I'm going [singing] to shout
till these walls come down. [music]
I see the [singing] light in Jesus name.
I'm going to laugh my fears away. I'm
going [music and singing] to dance till
these walls come down.
[music]
There's a song in my spirit.
There's a joy in my soul. Come what will
come what may I worship anyway. [music]
Oh the devil [singing] can try it. Try
to quiet the [music] song but I'll sing
out even louder than before.
I'm [music and singing] going to lift my
voice and sing. I'm going to give him
everything. I'm going
[music and singing] to shout till these
walls come down.
I see the light in [music and singing]
Jesus name. I'm going to laugh my fears
away. [music] I'm going [singing] to
dance till these walls go down.
Oh, we thank you for your [music]
[singing]
let's declare [music] this today. Say
the spirit of [singing] joy breaking
out. We can feel it all [music] around.
How we walked in [singing] won't be how
we're leaving. [music]
[singing]
>> He is doing something new. And we know
that [music and singing] he's not
through. It's the name of Jesus. We
believe you.
>> Oh, spirit of joy.
>> Spirit [music and singing] of joy
breaking out. We feel it all around.
[music]
how we walked [singing] in behind.
[music and singing]
[singing]
[music]
[music and singing]
I'm going to shout till these walls
[singing] go down. [music]
Oh, when I see the light in Jesus name,
I'm going to laugh [singing and music]
my fears away. I'm going to dance till
these walls [singing] go down.
I'm [music] going to dance till these
walls go down. [singing]
I'm going to [music] dance till these
walls go down.
praise in this place. [music]
Hallelujah.
Oh, we bless your [singing] name, Jesus.
>> Come on. Do we have a praise in the
house of the Lord this morning? [music]
I've got [singing] a praise that will
break off any chains. I've got a song
[music] that makes hell begin [singing]
to shake. I've got a shout that breaks
[music] their man from their graves.
Going to let it out. Going to let it
out. Going to let it out.
We [music] worship you.
Why would I ever [music] stay silent
when you are the one [singing] who told
me to speak? But how could [music] I
ever be quiet
when your spirit's in this authority?
[music and singing]
I'm not ashamed. I won't be [music]
afraid. You got to let [singing] it out.
I've got a praise that will break off
any chains. I've got a song
[music and singing] that makes hell
begin to shake. I've got a shout that
brings [music and singing] their men
from their
let it out. Go let it out. [music]
Let it out. [singing]
Why [music and singing] would I need
men's permission
when you're calling me [singing] to live
wild and free? Why [music] would I need
man's religion
when your spirit's [music] living inside
of me? I'm not ashamed. I won't
[singing] be afraid. Going to let it
[music] out. I've got a praise that will
break [singing] off heavy chains. I've
got a [music] song that they tell me to
say. I've got a [singing] shout that
brings them from
let it [music and singing] out.
Let it out. It's like a fire that
[music] shut up in my bones. It's like a
passion that's burning in my soul. It's
running wild [music and singing] and I'm
losing all control.
Let it out.
Let [music] it out.
>> [singing]
[music]
>> Oh, [singing] I'm going to sing till I
[music] have no voice. Even then, I'm
going to make some [singing] noise. I
[music] don't care what people say.
[singing] Cuz I'm going to praise you
anyway.
I'm going [music and singing] to sing
till I have no voice. Even then, I'm
going to make some noise. I don't
[music and singing] care what people say
cuz I'm going to praise you
[music and singing] anyway.
I'm going to sing till I have no voice.
Even then, I'm going to make
[singing and music] some noise. I don't
care what people say. I'm going to
praise [music] you anyway.
I've got a praise that will break off
[music and singing] heavy chains. I've
got a song that makes hell begin to
shake. [singing] I've got a shout that
brings dead men from their [music] gra.
Let it out.
Let it out. It's like a fire that shut
up in my bones. It's like a passion
[music]
that's [singing] burning in my soul.
It's running wild and I'm losing all
[music and singing] control. Going to
let it out. Going to let it out. Going
to let it out. [music and singing]
Yeah, we worship you.
Oh, come on. Let praise unto the Lord in
this place. Hallelujah.
Oh, we bless your name, Jesus.
[music and singing]
He's such a good and a faithful God.
Amen.
>> Let's lift our hands and let's just
[music] worship him in this place. Oh,
we thank you Lord.
Oh, we bless your name Jesus.
You are [music and singing] so good, so
faithful God.
You're my
strength. Though the [singing] earth
pass away the new remains
and it is written
that you provide [singing]
every need
everywhere that you [music] lead.
For you keep your [singing and music]
promises,
your [music and singing] goodness
never ends.
From [music and singing] generation
to generation, [singing]
[music]
you keep your covenant.
Oh, we see [music and singing]
your faithfulness
from [singing and music] generation
to generation.
[singing]
It is written,
we're redeemed [music]
by your [singing] blood. All the old has
passed away. The new has come.
For it is written,
it's not by [singing and music] power or
might, but by the spirit of the
[singing] living God in love.
You keep your [music and singing]
promise.
>> Your goodness never ends.
>> Your goodness
never [music]
ends. [singing]
generations
from generation
to [music and singing] generation
and you keep your covenant.
I [singing] see your faithfulness
[music]
[singing] for generation
[music] from generation
to generation. [singing]
Oh, come on. Just lift your [music]
hands and thank [singing] the Lord. He's
a faithful God. Oh, we thank you, Jesus.
Oh, we [music and singing] thank you,
Lord.
We will [music] trust you and believe.
Let [music and singing] it be. You alone
will be a fine foundation.
[music and singing]
And what you spokeen is enough. And it's
the crown [singing] we're standing on.
You are God. And we [music] will not be
shen.
Oh, [music] we will trust you and
[singing] believe. As it's written, let
it [music] be. Cuz you alone [singing]
will be a firm foundation.
>> What [music] is enough is a crown we're
[singing] standing on. You are God
[music] and we will not [singing] be
shen.
[music]
You keep [music]
your promises [singing]
never [music] end. Your goodness is
never [music]
>> from generation
to generation. [music]
And you keep your cup [singing]
for your faithfulness.
[music]
[singing] Faithfulness
generation. [music] From generation to
generation [singing]
to generation
generation [music] generation
to generation [music] generation
>> generation
to gener
>> [music]
>> Oh, we thank you for your faithful name.
Oh, we thank you.
Hey.
Come on, lift your hands and just
worship him this morning. We thank you,
Lord.
He's a faithful [music] God.
Oh, we worship you, Jesus.
We worship you Lord.
Thank you Lord.
What has [singing] washed away [music]
my s?
Nothing [music and singing] but the
blood
of Jesus
[music]
and what has [singing] made me whole
again.
Nothing [singing]
[music] but the blood
of Jesus.
[singing]
>> [music]
>> Oh, and [singing] what has [music]
washed away
my [singing] sin?
Nothing but the [music] blood
of [singing] Jesus.
And what [music]
has made me whole [singing]
again? [music]
Nothing but the blood
of Jes. [music]
[singing]
[music]
Nothing [music]
but the blood
of Jesus.
[singing and music]
has made me whole again.
[music and singing]
We sing nothing but the light
of Jesus. [music]
[singing]
And
[music] preious
is [singing] the love [music]
that
makes me [music] white [singing]
as snow.
[singing]
I [music] know
nothing but [singing] the blood
of Jesus. [music]
Operation
precious
is [music and singing] thous
[music]
[singing]
of [music] Jesus.
Thank you for your love.
[music and singing] Thank you for your
love.
[music]
>> [singing]
>> Oh, I thank you.
Oh, precious.
[music]
Preious [singing]
is [music] the love
that
makes me [music] white as [singing]
snow.
>> [music and singing]
>> bound
[music] nothing but the [singing] blood
of Jesus.
And how [music]
[singing] precious
is the blood
[music] that [singing]
makes me white as [music and singing]
snow. Oh no
other [music] found
[singing]
nothing [music] but the blood
of [singing] Jesus.
[singing]
Oh nothing but the blood [music]
Jesus.
Oh, come on [singing] church. We thank
you for his love.
[music]
We thank you [singing] for
your love.
>> Thank you for your [music]
[singing]
sing. So precious
and [music]
preious
is [singing] the glow
that
makes me [music]
white as [singing] snow.
[music]
I know
nothing [singing]
but the blood
of [music] Jesus.
[singing]
>> There's nothing but the blood.
[music and singing]
>> There's nothing but the blood
for those [music] who worship you. We
[singing] thank you. We praise you,
Lord.
>> We thank you for your
love. Thank you.
[music] Thank you, [singing] Lord. Thank
you, Lord. Come on, church. One more
time, let's just lift our hands and
[music] say thank you.
>> Oh, he [singing] really came
[music]
for us.
So we [music and singing] say thank you
Lord.
We say [music and singing] thank you.
We say thank [music] you.
We [singing and music] say
thank you.
Say [singing] thank you.
Thank you Jesus.
>> Thank you Jesus [music and singing] for
Jesus.
Just stay in this position of worship,
this place of worship.
Tap into the presence of God.
>> We thank you, Lord. We acknowledge your
presence today.
We say yes to you today.
We move with you today, Holy Spirit.
Thank you, Lord.
We thank you, Lord.
You know, we serve a God who is [music]
the same yesterday, today, and forever.
>> And I [music] love singing about this
because and it's and I think for some
people when you're new to this, it's
like, man, why are we singing about
blood? This is kind of strange. But see,
the blood of Jesus bought and paid for
us to be free, to be washed clean. You
know, we're learning about our covenant
with God. And when we sing about the
blood, what we're singing about is what
he did for us. The sacrifice paid for us
to redeem us and to set us free. And
where does that come from? What is the
purpose of that? Why? What drove God to
that? What drove Jesus to that? I've
been really [music] meditating on the
love of God.
Because that's that's the driving force
behind the sacrifice [music]
of Jesus. The love of God. And see, you
can grow up, especially if you grow up
in the church and you hear about the
love of God and you sing Jesus loves me,
this I know and it be it can become too
familiar and [music] start being head
knowledge instead of revelation
knowledge. And when the love of God is
revelation knowledge to us, there is
something that it it does in you. There
is a boldness that [music] it creates in
you. I want to read this passage in
first John
chapter [music] 4 and verse 9.
It says, "In this was manifested the
love of God [music] toward us, because
that God sent his only begotten son into
the world that we might live through
him.
Herein is love, not that we loved God,
but that he loved us and sent his son to
be the perpetuation for our sins."
I love that passage.
is not about you loving God.
That happens as a byproduct of a
revelation of the fact that he loves us.
He loves you in your mess, in your
imperfection, in your shortcomings, in
all the places that you He knows you
fully and loves you. How many of us can
really say we have anybody else in this
life that really loves us like that? I
mean, it's a it's a blessing if you've
experienced that kind of love. But it's
rare for somebody to fully know you,
everything about you, every hidden
thing, and to love you completely and
not just love you, but do something with
that. Send his son to die for you. Guys,
if you could get a revelation of this,
see what I've been studying out is love
is the foundation for all of the the
things that we walk in. How can we be
healed? Because he loves us. How can we
prosper? Because he loves us. How can we
be free from anxiety, depression, fear,
all the things that plague us? Because
he loves us.
And so what we do when those things come
at us, we say, "Who do you think you
are? I am the beloved of God.
What right do you have to touch me? You
have no right. You know, I think about
it like this. Okay, mamas, you can
relate to this. I'm sure daddies can
too, but you know, there is something
that comes out in you when somebody
comes after your kids. They call it a
mama bear, right? Someone comes after
your kids. There is something that comes
out of you. Sometimes it's not pretty,
but you want to you want to protect your
child, right? and you're going to do
what's necessary to protect your child.
How much more does our God love you, his
child, that if the enemy is after you,
you need to just stand up and say, "You
know what? He's my God. What do you
think you're doing? You have no right to
me." And then we stand in the love of
God. See, that's the healing isn't about
works. It's not about attaining this.
It's not about performance. It's about
recognizing [music] who loves you and
what belongs to you as a result of the
love.
Amen.
>> I want to pray over you. Father, I just
declare right now. [music] And I pray
that every single person in here will
see evidence of your love for [music]
them right now, all day long, today, all
week long. Father, that you will reveal
your [music] immense, great,
immeasurable, unending, unconditional
love for them. that they will see it and
know that they are loved without fail,
without any kind of condition, no matter
who who how they behave, no matter what
they do. God, that you love them. I
thank [music] you, Father, for a re a
revealing of this love. And Father, I
pray that we as carriers [music] of that
love will bring that revelation to
others in the way that we love them. and
we will be a vessel [music] of your love
for others.
I thank you for that, God.
I thank you for giving us revelation
within our hearts that would completely
transform the way we live our lives.
We love [music] you and we praise you.
In Jesus name we pray. Amen. Amen. You
[music] guys can be seated.
Well, good morning and welcome to
Movement Church. I don't know about you,
but there is no place I'd rather be on a
Monday, a Sunday [music] morning. Monday
morning, too. Sunday morning. I love
coming to church. Uh we had to miss
[music] last week and it was like I
didn't know what to do with myself being
out one week. We don't like missing. I
want to be here every Sunday. This is
the greatest [music] group of people I
know. Amen. Well, if this is your first
time, uh we want to welcome you. We want
to say thank you for coming. We want to
say that we are so glad that you are
here and we would love to invite you to
fill out a connection card. [music]
Uh you can do that by scanning the QR
code on the screen in front of you. Um
you can do that by tapping the little
circles on the seat back in front of
you. It'll take you to [music] a place
where you can fill that out. Um we also
want to invite you to pick up a welcome
packet. If this is your first time, we
want to just say welcome. [music] We
want to give you a little information
about the church. Um there's a message
in here from our pastors [music] and
there's a gift card to Summer Moon. I
mean, who doesn't want that, right? So,
if you if this is your first time or if
you've been before, [music] but you
haven't picked one of these up, be sure
you do that before you leave today. Uh
we would love to bless you and just say
thank you for being here. Um every week
we say our confessions. Uh you know, the
the vision of this church is moving
people from where they are to where God
is [music] calling them to be. Okay?
It's life, freedom, and fulfillment.
It's helping you [music] to find life
through Jesus, the only one that can
lead us into true life. And upon
following him, you walk in freedom from
anything that's ever held you back in
life. And then as you walk in that
freedom, then you will live in what it
looks like to truly be fulfilled. I have
never been [music] more fulfilled in my
entire life than in what I am doing
today. Never. [music] And it just keeps
getting better.
life with the Lord. When you're walking
closely to him and you're growing and
you're learning [music] about him more,
it just gets better. That's the will of
God anyways. So, if [music] you're not
seeing that in your life, I want to
invite you to get connected here. Start
serving [music] here because when you
begin to serve and you begin to submit
yourself humbly to the Lord, you will
begin to do things that you never
thought you could do. And in that you
will see that growth and that [music]
transformation.
With this though, with this growth, this
church begins to grow. We've got more
people. It's full every week, right? We
need more space. And we don't we talk
about this because we keep the vision in
front of us every week. You know, the
Bible tells us to do that. [music] And
we are growing. We're getting land.
We're building buildings. The school
right now is pre-K through [music] third
grade at second grade this year. And
we'll be growing all the way up through
12th. 12th grade. Well, if you walk
around this building at all, that don't
fit here.
But that's the calling of God. So, the
calling of God is to build a school
pre-K through 12th grade. Well, if
that's the calling of God, that means
he's got something more to fulfill that.
And so, we say every week these
confessions so that we don't forget this
is where we're [music] going. This isn't
where we're staying. We are moving from
here. So, I want to invite you uh to say
these [music] with us by faith,
believing in where God is calling our
church.
All grace abounds towards us. We have
everything we [music] need to accomplish
all that God has called us to do. We
thank you Lord for the provision to
build all the buildings needed for
Movement Church, [music] Movement
Christian Academy, Movement Bible
College, and every work you call us to
do. We say yes to your [music] plan, and
we thank you for your grace to complete
our assignment. We call this done
[music] in Jesus' name. Amen. Amen.
Well, as we prepared to receive [music]
our tithes and offering, I want to read
a passage to you. There was a story that
I was reading and man, it got me fired
[music] up. So, every week, I am so
thankful for a pastor
uh that desires [music] to teach us what
the word says about everything.
and especially with finances. I have
learned so much in this [music] area and
grown so much in this area and we've
seen such fruit in this area. And so
it's so exciting to me [music]
um when I get to share this because I
believe there is so much power in
knowing the truth behind God's will for
[music] your finances. Okay? And and
like I'm saying, God is growing us.
Well, the way he's [music] going to do
that is through you, through the people
of this church sewing into what God is
doing [music] here. So I was reading
this story about Elijah in first kings
chapter [music] 17 and Elijah tells Ahab
just to summarize he tells Ahab it's not
going to rain the king you know [music]
and that makes someone not very happy
when the prophet says things that are
not good for you. So he flees and God is
taking care of him by this [music] river
providing the water and the birds are
bringing him food. Well the river dries
up because there's no rain, right? And
so God's going to move him somewhere
else because [music] when God tells you
to do something and you're obedient, you
can trust he's going to provide for you
every time. So in [music] in chapter
17:9,
he gives these instructions to Elijah
and he says, "Arise, get thee to
Zerapath, which belongs to Zidon, and
dwell there. Behold, I have commanded a
widow woman there to sustain [music]
you." So Elijah goes, and when he gets
there, he sees this woman. and she's
picking [music] up sticks. And I think
it's so interesting because it says here
he's commanded her, which means this
woman's always already been given some
kind of instructions by the Lord. So
when Elijah goes to her, he says, "Go
get me a drink first." And then she's
going. And as she's going, he says,
"Also, bring me some bread." And the
woman [music] says, "I don't have any
bread. All I have is a little bit of
flour and a little bit of oil. And I was
just about to go take these sticks, make
this [music] for me and my son, and then
we're going to die. They've got nothing.
They're starving.
What an interesting person for the Lord
to send Elijah to to sustain him.
Isn't that interesting? You know, it
would seem logical for God to send
Elijah to someone that's wealthy, who's
got a lot of food to sustain him, but
that's not what God does. See, that's
not how God does things. I think so many
times we think we need to be the
wealthiest person in the room in order
to be able to contribute to the mission.
God used a widow woman who is planning
to die because of she that they have
nothing.
So then this is the good the best part.
So then Elijah says, "Okay, you go do
that. You go make that, but you feed me
first.
Feed me first, then feed you and your
son." I mean, talk about taking another
step. Give me every what you have, but
don't feed yourself. You're starving. I
get that. But feed me. Oh my goodness.
How many people have heard [music] a
message where the where the minister
said, "Take, give me what you got. I
know you're starving, but take care of
me first." How many people be like,
"Blasy. I'm leaving this place."
I love God because see, when she was
obedient to what the Lord commanded her
to do, not only did the Lord sustain
Elijah, but now her flour and oil did
not run out the entire time [music]
Elijah was staying with her. the whole
time for years. He was with her for
years, two to three years. And in that
time, her son [music] gets sick and he
makes him well. There is benefit when
you decide and make up your mind, Lord,
when you command me to give. [music]
Whether I have little, whether I have
much, I'm going to be obedient to that.
There is something [music] phenomenally
supernatural that will come. I'm telling
you, you can trust God with your
finances. So much of the world, the
Christian world today, wants to give
when we feel emotional, wants to give
when we feel drawn to a cause, wants to
give because we feel like we've got
enough this month. [music] So now we're
going to give. That isn't biblical
giving.
Biblical giving is I am committing to
obedience to the Lord no matter what it
might cost me. And then when you step
out in that, it will cost you nothing.
You're going to be blessed. And and I I
read this quote this week and it says,
you know, we don't give to live. We are
not giving to get. We should expect it.
It is a promise, but that isn't the
heart behind it. We are to live to give.
Your existence should be to give.
And when you do, then you live
abundantly. Guys, God is so cool.
But he needs us to trust him in the
least [music] of these things, which is
finances. It's the least. If we can't
trust him in our finances, you're not
[music] trusting him in other areas. And
I can tell you that right now. It's the
least of those. I want to encourage you
today. If this is an area that has been
a struggle for you, just approach it
like this woman here. God, you've
commanded me to give to you, so I'm
doing it today. [music] And I'm just
going to trust that you'll do what you
say you would do. Amen. Let's pray.
Lord, we just thank you for your
faithfulness that when you say it, it is
done and you will fulfill it, that you
perform what you promise in your word.
And I thank you for that today, Father,
[music] that as as the people of this
church commit in this area, God, there
will be such a harvest that there will
not be room in this church to contain
it. that we'll have so much giving that
we would have to tell people to stop
because it [music] we is way more than
what we need. I thank you, Father, for
the provision in that. Thank you that we
will be able to do everything that we
are called to do as a church because of
[music] the faithfulness and the trust
in you. We love you, Lord. We surrender
everything that we have to you. In Jesus
name [music] we pray. Amen.
>> Amen. And boy, that's a good word,
wasn't it?
>> That was a good word. Did you Are you
ready to receive from the word today?
>> Did you come expecting today?
>> You know, I was uh I was I love what
Lindsay was sharing there because, you
know, so many times uh we look at
ourselves and our own ability and what
we have, but this woman didn't have
anything. And I find it funny, it's so
ironic how God does things, right? God
brought us here to Salana, Texas, and he
brought us here and and we have a church
full of you guys. And you might be
looking at your wallet saying, "I can't
afford that. I can't afford that." Well,
God's doing it again.
>> I said he's doing it again.
>> And you need to start thinking like this
woman was thinking, right? You need to
start thinking like her and be willing
to give and do whatever it is that God
calls you to do. Amen.
>> And when you do, as Lindsay was saying,
something supernatural happens on the
inside of you. Amen. How many you like
the supernatural?
>> Amen. Praise God. Well, I got a quick
dad joke for you before we get in the
word today. Y'all love my dad jokes,
right?
>> Come on now. This is a really good one.
What do you call a deer with no eyes?
>> No idea.
Who said that? [laughter]
Oh, the kids get my dad jokes. The kids
love my dad jokes. Here's another one.
How many names can also pass as numbers?
I can only think of one.
>> One. I can only think of one. One. You
love it. You love that one. I know you
did. Praise God. We're talking in this
series about covenant living. How to
live in your covenant. I believe this is
one of the most foundational things that
Christians do not know is how to live in
their covenant. Matter of fact, I go so
far as to say this. Most Christians
don't know anything about this. Most
Christians when you start talking to
them about their covenant with God, they
would probably look at you a little bit
strange because they don't know anything
about it. They don't know what it means
for them. All they know is we take
communion at church. That's all they
know. You know, I it's funny. I was uh
when I was working, I first started
working and I was in college. uh this
lady, we hired this lady to do a job and
she worked in the same area as me and
she was doing the side hustle thing at
the same time and she was uh selling
these like these water filtration
systems and she was making some flyers
up at work one day when she was going to
go out and start marketing, you know,
her little side hustle and start passing
these out. And she showed me a picture
of it of this advertisement that she
made and the advertisement says
something like this. Are you tired of
having all that chlorine in your water?
Are you tired of tasting chlorine in
your water? The problem was she spelled
chlorine. C H L O R I N G. Chlorine.
And I and I laugh, but you know, this
was not Chris. Now, this was like 21
year old Chris. I didn't say a word. I
thought, if you're not smart enough to
know how to spell chlorine, you don't
need to be selling water filtration
systems. They didn't know how to spell
it. And they had spellch check back
then. Yes, they did have spell check
back then. And and so that's that's how
I feel a lot of times about people and
their covenant, how Christians feel
about their covenant. They know a few
words. They know a little bit about it,
but they don't know really anything that
they're talking about. And so we've been
reading here in our foundational
scripture, Ephesians 2:11.
He said this, "Therefore remember that
you once Gentiles in the flesh, who are
called uncircumcision by what is called
the circumcision, made in the flesh by
hands, that at that time you were
without Christ, being aliens from the
commonwealth of Israel, and strangers
from the covenants of promise." Say
strangers.
>> Strangers.
>> What does that mean? That means you're
not aware of you're you're not familiar
with the covenants of promise. And look
what it says here. When you're in that
situation, look at you. It says, "Being
aliens of the commonwealth of Israel,
strangers from the covenants of
promises, having no hope and without God
in the world." You know, if you don't
activate your covenant promises, you're
without God's help in this world.
>> Amen. If you don't learn how to live in
your covenant, you will live your entire
life as a Christian wondering why this
is happening. How many people do you
know? How many Christians do you know
are waiting on God to heal them? How
many Christians do you know are waiting
on God to pour out financial provision
on them? How many Christians do you know
are begging and pleading with God to do
these things in their life? And they
that the reason they're doing that is
because they do not know their covenant.
They do not know what belongs to them.
They do not know that Jesus I said Jesus
has already done it for you.
>> He's already promised it.
>> Now, if I were to promise you something
and then you turn right around and
you're begging me to do it, you know
what that tells me? That tells me you
don't believe my word.
if I promised it. I said, "I promise,
Michelle, I'm going to buy you a
cheeseburger at McDonald's. I promise."
She's like, "No, please don't. No, I
promise I'm going I promise you." And
then and then she comes up to me and
says, "Pastor, could you buy me a
cheeseburger?" I mean, I I know you said
it, but I could you just tell me again.
Could you just I don't know. I don't
know if I can trust what you say. I
don't know if I could go actually go to
McDonald's and expect you to actually
hand me that cheeseburger and buy that
cheese. I mean, think about how how that
would be against my character and
against my nature. But that's exactly
what Christians do to God every single
day.
>> You you know, people that are he's
talking about people that don't have
Christ in this world being strangers to
the covenants of promise. But there are
many Christians today who are strangers
to the covenants of promise and they
don't trust God at all
>> with anything.
>> Look what it says here in verse number
13. But now say now.
>> Now,
>> now in Christ Jesus, you who were once
far off have been brought near by the
blood of Christ.
>> You're no longer a stranger to the
covenants of promise. You're supposed to
learn something.
We're supposed to be growing and
learning as Christians. Amen. Well,
pastors, when do you stop growing and
learning? That's what I want to know.
When have I arrived? I feel like I've
arrived. I feel like I already know some
things. When do I start? I mean, I've
read the Bible all the way through. Me
and Jamie, we've read the Bible all the
way through multiple times. I think I'm
there. Do you know what? As you're here
on this earth, you will never arrive.
There is no point where you arrive and
suddenly you don't you don't need to
keep growing and learning about your
covenant with God. Well, I've heard
teaching on this. Well, you're about to
hear some more
>> because you need to know your covenant
and and you find out how much you trust
in your covenant with God. When
something bad happens in your life,
>> you find out exactly where people are in
their belief in their covenant, in their
trust. Well, I don't know if I can trust
God's word. Well, I don't know if God's
going to come through for me. and
they're worried and they're afraid and
they're full of anxiety. You know, I
just described most people.
>> They're worried and they're afraid and
they have all this anxiety because they
don't know their covenant.
>> They don't know their God. They don't
know he's a covenant keeping God. And if
God said it,
>> well, come on, somebody.
>> If he said it, it is a covenant promise.
>> That means if he said it, he's going to
do it. That's right.
>> Because he said it, right?
If you can't trust his covenant
promises, then you don't understand your
God.
>> We read this last week. He said, "My
covenant I will not break."
>> What do you think? You think he means
that? Well, I don't know if I could
trust him.
>> I don't know if I could trust him with
my family. I don't know if I could trust
him with my finances. I don't know if I
can do that. He said he will not break
his covenant.
>> So, when you find a promise in the word
of God, you can stand on that promise.
you can believe what he said
>> because his covenant he will not break.
>> Amen.
>> So, we're going to dive a little bit
deeper here today. Oh man, we're going
to get some good stuff today.
>> It's going to be good. You know, at the
beginning of this year, the Lord spoke a
word to me. Y'all remember the the
series we taught at the beginning of
this year? The Lord spoke to me and
said, "2026
is a year of new beginnings.
>> It's a year of new beginnings." And we
taught a whole series on new beginnings.
what a new beginning is. And uh some of
you are probably thinking, you know,
here we are in July. Some of you are
probably thinking, well, when's a new
beginning going to start for me? You
know, I haven't seen a new beginning in
my 2026 yet. Well, perhaps you're not
standing in your covenant.
>> Perhaps we don't know enough about our
covenant promises to be able to step
into all that God has for us in 2026.
But let me tell you what, that ends
today.
>> Amen. Amen. So, let's read here in
Genesis chapter 17.
We're going to start in verse one, and
we're going to see something about our
covenant. In Genesis 17:1, it says,
"When Abram was 99 years old, the Lord
appeared to Abram and said to him, I am
Almighty God. Walk before me and be
blameless."
I am Almighty God. You know what he
said? He said, "I am El Shadai."
Of course, we've talked about this a
lot. You've heard me teach on this. This
means that that I am the God of all
sufficiency in all things. I am the God
of all provision. He didn't say, "I'm
the God of Walmart."
Now, you could go to Walmart and you
could get a lot of stuff, right? I mean,
you can get a lot of different kind of a
wide variety of stuff at Walmart. But he
didn't say, "I'm the god of Walmart."
What he was saying is, "I'm the God of
Walmart, Costco, HB, Kroger, uh, Academy
Sports. I'm the God that has all
sufficiency. Anything that you will ever
need in this life, I've got it."
>> That's a big announcement right there.
>> That is a huge announcement. If you're
ever going to need anything, you have
you don't have to look any place else
but to me.
>> Man, that that alone right there ought
to be enough for us, right? When you're
in need, when you're struggling with
something, he's El Shai.
>> You can go to him and get anything that
you need. He's better than Walmart.
>> He's better than Costco, Sam's Club,
right? He's better. I mean, everything
that you possibly need. How many you
know that uh I was it's kind of
interesting when you watch the World Cup
this year and all the people from other
countries, you know, coming into our
country and and seeing how America
actually is versus what the woke news
media talks about. And it's interesting
to hear all the comments, right? They're
just like, "Wow, this is amazing." And
they were I heard one guy talking about
Walmart, how you could you could go
there and get anything, right? They're
just amazed at all the things that we
have in America. And what they say is,
"It's not what we thought it was."
>> Yeah. because there's so much provision
here. Well, this is nothing compared to
El Shadai.
>> El Shadai has everything. So, Abram is
hearing this. He said, I'm El Shadai.
Look at verse number two.
And I will make my covenant between me
and you and will multiply you
exceedingly. Say exceedingly.
You know, God doesn't do anything on a
small scale.
>> Have you noticed that nothing that he
does is small?
>> It's all exceedingly.
>> It's all big.
>> He doesn't do things in a small way. He
created a universe so vast and so big we
don't even know. We can't even count.
Remember he told he told him he said,
"Go out and count the stars. count the
sand on the you can't even count it this
so big that's exceedingly
>> that means more than enough right so God
does things in to a great degree or
exceedingly look at verse three then
Abram fell on his face and God talked
with him saying
as for me you know in a covenant
relationship there are two parts God is
saying this is my part and you know he's
about to tell him what his part is it's
a two-way way street. A covenant
relationship is not a one-way street.
How many you know a marriage covenant is
not a one-way street.
>> It's not your way or the highway. Uh
that's not how a marriage works.
>> If you want to have a successful
marriage, it's a two-way street, right?
There's two people in this marriage.
It's not just one. So God said, "As for
me," he fell on his face. He said, "As
for me, my covenant is with you, and you
shall be a father of many nations." Now,
remember, he couldn't have kids.
Remember, he he tried to have a kid with
Hagar and had Ishmael, but he wasn't
able to have a child with Sarah, his
wife, or Sarah, his wife. Look at look
what it says here. Verse number five. No
longer shall your name be called Abram,
but your name shall be Abraham.
And I for I have made you a father of
many nations. So God changed his name.
Some of y'all need a name change.
>> Some of y'all need to know you've had a
name change.
>> Some of you need to know it's already
happened, but you don't know about your
covenant.
>> So he changed his name. We're going to
we're going to dive a little bit into
this today. Changed his name. If we're
going to jump down here in verse number
15, I love this. Then God said to
Abraham, "As for Sarai, your wife, you
shall not call her name Sarai, but Sarah
shall be her name, and I will bless her
and also give you a son by her."
And then they will then I will bless
her, and she shall be a mother of
nations. Kings of peoples shall come
from her. So, he changed Abram's name to
Abraham and he changed Sarah's name to
Sarah.
Aren't you glad, ladies, he didn't just
do it for the man?
>> Come on, ladies. I know it's not
Mother's Day, but you can say amen to
that one. Aren't you glad that what God
is no respector of persons and it's not
just a male oriented Christianity that
God will his covenant promises are just
as much for you than it is the man.
>> Ladies,
>> God is not holding back on you.
>> He wasn't doing things for Abram he
wasn't going to do for Sarah.
>> But I want you to notice something. They
needed a name change.
They needed a name change. And before
Abram and Sarai could not have kids,
they couldn't reproduce. But I what I
want you to see this morning is that
Abraham
and Sarah can.
>> What I want you to see this morning is
Abraham and Sarah in their covenant can.
>> Amen. They got access to something now
they didn't have access to before.
>> Can you see something's happening here?
>> Abram and Sarai could not have a baby,
but covenant man Abraham and covenant
woman Sarah can.
>> What am I telling you? When you begin to
function and operate in your covenant,
there are things that God's going to do
in you and through you that you can't do
right now.
>> You're not able to even see it or even
do it. This is beyond what you've ever
dreamed. You're like Abram and Sarah,
not able to have a baby, and you've been
walking around saying, "We can't have a
baby. We can't have a baby. Oh, wo is
me." And God is saying, "You need to
look at your covenant. Amen.
>> You need to know that your name has
changed.
>> And not only did he change their names,
but did you know God changed his name,
too?
>> Did you know that? What did he what did
he announce himself as after this
moment? Everywhere after this, he says,
"I'm the God of Abraham.
>> I'm the God of Abraham, of Isaac, of
Jacob." Why? Because this was a
generational covenant. It didn't die
with Abram or Abraham. It didn't die
with him. It was passed on to I. That's
why the circumcision, the sign or the
mark of the covenant was in the
reproductive system of the man because
it was a reproductive covenant. It was
to go from generation to generation to
generation. And it wasn't going to end
with Abram.
>> Amen.
>> So God changed his name. He said, "You
need a name change is what you need,
Abram. I'm going to change your name to
Abraham. I'm going to change her name to
Sarah." So, what did he do when he
changed their names? Let's look at it
here. First, let's I just want to take a
look at God's name. You got that first
graphic? Put that up there. This is
God's proper name. Now, we call him God.
That's kind of a general term. And
anytime you see God translated in the
Old Testaments, it's typically Elohim
or Elohim. I say Elohim. Elohim. But I'm
from Oklahoma, so I could do that.
Elohim. Elohim. And that's kind of God's
plural name. That's like saying God. But
you know, God has a specific name.
That's like saying, uh, I'm a male.
That's kind of general, right? That's
true. I'm a male or I'm a guy or I'm a
boy. And it's it's it's really simple to
know that, right? We know why I'm a boy
and why, you know,
it's not confusing, is it?
>> Amen.
>> But I also have a name. My name is
Chris. Right? That's my specific name.
Well, you know, God has a name. And this
is God's name. We we translate it
Jehovah or sometimes it's translated in
English Yahweh, but it's only four
letters. In the Hebrew, there are no
vows. So God's name, his proper name, I
don't know if you can see that up there.
His proper name is four letters. So the
first one here is the letter we would we
would call a Y, but it's actually y. The
second one is hey. The third one is vav.
And the fourth one is hey.
So you can see there when you put y, w
or y, and then h again, you can see
where you put in a couple of vowels.
It's Yahweh.
That's where we get the ter the the
word. That's why we get we say it in
English because in English we got to
have some vows.
Can I buy a vow? Right. We had to buy
some vows to put it in there because
there's no vows in the Hebrew. So for it
to make sense, we had to put vows in
there. But that's actually God's name
right there. So now let's take a look at
Abraham's name. Let's put the Abraham up
here. What do you notice about Abraham's
name? There's a letter that was inserted
from Abram to Abraham. And it's, you can
see here the A B R and then M. That was
Abram. But there was a letter that was
inserted there. You see the H.
One letter. One letter was changed from
Abram to Abraham. And it was the letter
Hey.
Now, let's pull up Sarah's.
Pull hers up. Same thing right at the
very end of Sarah's name. Sarah doesn't
isn't spelled this way, but Sarah has
the letter hey at the end of it. Why am
I pointing this out? Because God's name
is Yadhee vi.
So God took a letter part of his name
and he put it in his covenant partner's
name. Yeah.
>> And he took that not just for Abram, but
he did it for Sarah, too.
>> And he put his name in your name.
>> You see that?
>> That's how he changed their name. He put
his name in their name. So, okay,
pastor, why is that so significant?
Well, we need to understand some things
about Hebrew letters. They're not like
English letters.
Hebrew letters themselves have meaning.
You know, our letters don't have a lot
of meaning. We don't have some of them
do, but most of them don't. Our our
English is weird. I think English is one
of the most challenging languages to
learn. I'm still trying to learn it. My
English ain't very good.
Because, you know, we say so many
things, right? We we have these phrases
and these words that mean the same. They
sound the same, but they're different
and they mean different things. It's
just so weird. I can't imagine trying to
learn English. Can you?
But the Hebrew language is very
different and unique because letters
have meanings. And this letter hey has a
meaning. Do you want to know what the
meaning is? Here's the meaning of the
letter hey. It means breath of life.
It means something that's revealed.
It means
grace.
Grace. God's grace. It means power. It
means the spirit.
>> Can you see what God was doing here?
>> He didn't just put He didn't just change
his name, right? Well, we know that's a
part of a covenant, right? The the names
change. And you see that in covenant
partners all the time. There's always
the name change. We get married and in
our culture the the wife changes her
name, right? Takes on the name of a
husband. But many cultures, they share
the same name. Put a hyphen in it.
And so God put his his that letter hey
from his name into Abram's name and into
Sarah's name. And when he did that, he
was putting his grace there. He was
putting his spirit there. He was putting
his power there.
>> Amen.
>> And Abram could not have a child. But
Abraham with the grace of God, with the
spirit of God can.
Sarah I could not either, but Sarah can.
Well, well, pastor, what does this mean
for us? I mean, why? Okay, good for
them, but what does this mean for us?
Did you know that you've been given a
name?
>> Did you know that when you were born
again, you were given what happens when
you get born again? The spirit of God
comes to live on the inside of you,
>> inserted on the inside of you. You got
God's spirit. And not only did you
receive the spirit of God, you received
also his grace.
>> Did you or did you not?
>> Matter of fact, the Bible says the
fullness of the Godhead bodily.
>> You got it all.
>> Not just one little aspect. You got all
of him.
>> You didn't just get part of God. You got
all of him on the inside of you. So when
you accept Jesus as your personal
savior, God does the same thing only
better.
>> And then you got a name change. What
name did you get?
Some of you are like, I don't know,
pastor, but it sounds good.
[laughter]
It's not complicated. I'm not trying to
trick you. Let's read about the name you
got. Philippians chapter 2 verse number
eight. and being found in appearance as
a man, talking about Jesus now, he
humbled himself and became obedient to
the point of death, even the death of
the cross. Therefore, God also has
highly exalted him and given him the
name which is above every name.
>> What name is above every name?
The name of Jesus. Right? that at the
name of Jesus,
every knee should bow
>> of those in heaven, of those on earth,
and of those under the earth. Well, that
covers a lot of territory, doesn't it?
>> And that every tongue should confess.
Why we say a confession every week?
Because God is a confession God. We need
to agree with him. I need to say what he
says. That's what a confession is. Every
sh every tongue should confess that
Jesus Christ is Lord to the glory of God
the father.
So the name that we have is the name of
Jesus.
And it's not just the name, it's the
name above every other name. It's the
name that's greater than every other
name. It's the name that's more powerful
than any other name.
>> And I can tell by your reactions
already, we don't understand our
covenants very well.
>> Because I just talked about how Abraham
could do things with his name change
that he couldn't do before. Why? Because
he received the grace. He received the
spirit of God, the power of God on his
life. And when you got born again, you
received the spirit of God. You receive
the grace of God. And you and I have
been given a name.
>> And it's not just any old name. Wouldn't
that been funny? I'm Bill.
We'll give you a name. Bill. Just a just
a random Bill. Just plain old random.
What's What's significant about that?
Nothing.
Just I just given you a name. No. This
name has meaning.
This name has power.
>> This name has authority. Look at this in
Mark chapter 16
verse number 17. It says, "And these
signs will follow those who believe
in my name."
>> What was he doing? He's given us his
name.
>> In my name. What are you supposed to do?
They will cast out demons
in my name.
In my name, they will speak with new
tongues.
Boy, I tell you what, we've eliminated a
lot of the body of Christ already,
haven't we?
>> Well, you talking about demonic stuff. I
don't anything to do with that because
I'm scared of demons. Why would you be
scared of a demons? You got a new name.
>> Why would any Christian be afraid of the
devil
>> or a demon?
Why? Tell me why. Because they don't
know their covenant.
>> And they don't know they've received a
name.
>> They don't know it. They're strangers to
the covenants of promise. have no idea
of what actually happened to them when
they got born again. Can you see how
deceptive the devil is? He does not want
you to know this.
>> The last thing he wants is a bunch of
Christians running around this earth
that know their covenant with God.
>> That's the last thing he wants.
Christians that don't know their
covenant are no problem for him at all.
>> Why? Because they're not going to
resist. They're not going to stand on
their covenant promises. They're not
going to confess their covenant
promises. They're not going to do
anything. They're going to be afraid of
the devil. They're going to be afraid of
some kind of a bug, a stomach bug.
Let me let me say it another way.
Stomach parasite.
They'll be afraid of some some virus or
some disease. And I know every I know
y'all know what I'm talking about. It's
getting close to home now, isn't it?
Shouldn't you be? Well, pastor, we
should be afraid. We should respect
these things. Really,
my Bible doesn't say that. My Bible says
I've been given a name.
>> I got a name change. I'm no longer Chris
Carter.
>> When I accepted Jesus as my savior, I am
now Chris Carter in Christ.
[applause]
>> You see, God put me in his name.
>> [laughter]
>> He put his name in Abram's name. He put
you in his name.
>> Are we getting it?
>> He put you in his name. I am Chris
Carter in Christ. It's not just me.
We're in covenant together. I am Chris
Carter in Christ. I've been given his
name. And it says the name above every
names that that you can cast out demons
in these names. You can speak with
tongues. If they take up serpents and if
they drink anything deadly, it will by
no means hurt them.
>> I could eat that nasty virus or I can
eat that bacteria or whatever it is,
that bug. I could eat it for breakfast.
I'm not telling you to go eat it for
breakfast.
I'm just saying that you could eat See,
here's here's where we go. Here's this
is where the rubber meets the road,
guys. Do you know your covenant or not?
Yeah.
>> Because many times what we will do is we
will do something like that and we'll
eat something and it's like, man, I knew
when I was eating that that wasn't any
good. I think I've got food poisoning.
And then what do you expect to happen
after that? You start feeling it, right?
Everybody Everybody's experienced that.
But what's the Bible say? You can eat
something deadly in your covenant. Well,
Chris Carter eats something deadly, it's
it's going to be bad for him. But Chris
Carter in Christ,
>> I said Chris Carter in Christ could eat
something deadly
and I'm not even affected by it.
>> Doesn't automatically happen though,
does it? You got to know this.
>> And not only do you have to know it,
you're going to have to do something
about it when you know it.
>> What we're finding out is many many
people don't really know it, or if they
kind of know it, they don't really do
anything about it.
because they got more faith in a in a
bug, a parasite, a virus. They got more
faith in a doctor's report. They got
more trust in in somebody else's word
than God's word.
>> When God said, "My covenant I will not
break."
>> The Bible says that our covenant that we
have is a better covenant than what they
had.
>> It's better. That means if if they
couldn't have kids, but now the covenant
man, Abraham and Sarah can have kids. If
you're having trouble having children,
>> come on, somebody.
>> If you're experiencing the same thing
they're experiencing, a better covenant
would not mean you can't either.
Well, he did it for them, but he
wouldn't do it for me. You don't know
your covenant.
>> You're stranger to the covenant of
promise. Have no idea. It says that we
could cast out demons. We could take up
serpents. If they drink anything deadly,
it will by no means hurt them.
>> Oh, I love that. They will lay hands on
the sick. Who's going to lay hands on
the sick?
>> The covenant man.
>> The covenant woman will lay hands on.
We're talking about a covenant man. Not
just any old man. A covenant man as
someone who knows their covenant, living
in their covenant. We know this from
from scripture. You remember when these
guys tried to go out there and cast a
demon out of somebody, seven sons
ofKeva, and they tried to cast a demon
out, and the demon
thrashed them,
>> beat them up, stripped them naked,
bleeding, hurting, and they were trying
to do it, but they didn't have a
covenant,
>> and they didn't even know anything about
it. They said in the name of Jesus that
Paul preaches about. They weren't in the
covenant. They had no idea what this
was. They had no idea how. They just saw
Paul doing it. So they said, "Well,
let's go give it a shot. Let's just try.
Let's let's look at exactly how he did
it. Let's create a formula and then
let's go over here and repeat the
formula and see if it works."
That's not covenant.
>> But you know, that's how a lot of
Christians do things.
>> Oh, we're bad about that.
We are so bad about that. I'll tell you
who's really bad about it. It's pastors.
Churches. Well, what's working for them?
Oh, you know what? They got this and
that and they bought these fancy lights.
So, we better get those. Oh, and you
know what they do? They get up here and
they don't say, "I'm the lead pastor."
They say, "I'm the lead communicator at
Movement Church."
That'll do it. And their church grew by
like 10 times, right? So, let's go do
what they've been doing. I've been to
many church uh conferences in my life.
And you know, that's a lot of what they
are.
>> Here's what we do. Just take this and go
do it at your church. Well, I'm not
saying that there's not things you can
learn from other people. I'm not saying
there's not good practices and things
like that, but nothing. I said nothing.
I said nothing replaces the leading of
the Holy Spirit.
>> And and I got news for you. You ready?
You're not the Holy Spirit.
>> I'm not the Holy Spirit. I got him in
me. You've got him in you. But you're
not the Holy Spirit. I'm not led by you.
I'm led by the spirit.
>> I'm not led by what they're doing. I'm
not led by what they're doing. But
that's exactly what the seven sons ofKea
did. And guess what? We laugh about that
story. They're bleeding and naked.
[laughter]
How many Christians are bleeding and
naked right now?
bleeding, hurting,
>> broken,
>> no hope, and they're wondering why. And
they they read the Bible all the way
through, but they don't know,
>> because they don't know how to live in
their covenant. They don't know the
covenant promises, and they don't know
how to activate the covenant promises.
Do you know how Abram did this?
Abram, now think about this. God spoke
to him directly. He didn't announce it
to everybody. He didn't even announce it
to everybody that was on the earth. He
spoke it to him.
>> You're going to be the father of many
nations. I'm changing your name. It's
now going to be Abraham. I'm putting my
name in your name. So now think about
this. The very first drop out of the
hat, what happens? Abram walks out, goes
outside the next day, and someone says,
"Hey, Abram, he's got a choice, doesn't
he?" Oh, here's where the rubber meets
the road, isn't it? He's got a choice.
What does he say? Um, no, no, no, no. My
name's not Abram anymore. It's Abraham.
>> And Abraham means the father of a
multitude.
[laughter]
>> So, he just went out there and said,
"Don't call me Abram anymore. Call me
Abraham. Call me the father of a
multitude, a father of many." When he
had, you know, couldn't have kids with
Sarah.
Day after day after day, constantly.
Hey, Abram. I know you don't know yet,
>> but let me go ahead and tell you, I'm
not Abram anymore. I'm Abraham.
>> You see, I have a covenant with God.
>> He's changed my name. He's given me his
name. I'm now Abraham, the father of
many. How many times do you think
Abraham had to do that?
>> More than once?
>> Probably more than twice. probably day
after day after day, he was probably
challenged with it.
How does that relate to us? Well, day
after day after day, you've got people
challenging you. You've got the devil
challenging you. Oh, you're never going
to be Oh, you're probably going to catch
this. This is going around. Not this
covenant guy.
>> Well, this happens to everybody. It's
just going around. Everybody's going to
get it. Not this guy.
Not this covenant man. Not this covenant
woman. I have a new name.
[laughter]
When you when you yell and say, "Hey,
poor boy. Come here. I'm not coming
>> because that's not me.
>> Hey sick man, get over here. I'm not
sick. I'm not coming."
You see what I'm saying?
When people speak against you and the
covenant that you have, most Christians
speak against it themselves.
>> And they call themselves something
they're not.
>> Well, you know, I'm just old sinner. No,
you're not.
>> You were before, but now you're not.
Well, you know, this virus goes around,
everybody gets it, and I'll probably
It's just going to go through everybody,
and I'm going to get it, and my brother
will get it, my sister will get it, my
kids will get it, my husband will get
it, and we'll probably get it. It'll
probably last couple weeks. You know,
that's not what a covenant man says.
>> A covenant man says what his covenant
partner said about it, and that no evil
shall befall you, nor any plague go near
your dwelling.
>> Amen. Remember we just titled Psalms 91.
>> He'll give his angels charge over you.
He could eat anything deadly and it
won't hurt you. What if it's demonic?
What if it is? You've got authority.
Why? Because you have been given a name.
>> And it's not just any old random name,
Bill. It's the name above
every other name. Give me a name.
Give me a name.
>> Pete.
>> What' you say? Pete. [laughter]
>> No, I mean something.
>> Cancer is a name.
>> Heart disease is a name, Pete. Man, I
hope if there's a Pete watching online,
I'm sorry
that I didn't say it.
Jesus loves you, Pete.
Probably short for Peter. He was a
disciple. Amen.
Give me a name.
>> There you go.
>> Uh, autoimmune disease.
>> I mean, you can just keep going, right?
Just keep going. Keep going and keep
going. And when you go to the doctor and
they said, doctor says, "This is what
you have." You need to tell them, "Well,
I know you don't understand, doc, but
see I'm in covenant with God. Yes,
>> Abram had that, but Abraham doesn't.
>> I've been given a name.
>> I got a new name now.
>> That means something.
>> That means I don't have to have that.
>> That means I'm no longer not going to
have the ability or the grace to have
children. I've been given a name.
>> And it's the name above every other
name.
>> He has put our name in his name.
>> Yes.
I'm Chris Carter in Christ. You know,
you need to see yourself that way. I'm
Josh Swink in Christ. It's not just me
anymore. You know, when you get married,
it's not just you anymore.
>> Have you figured that one out?
>> It's not just you anymore. You can't
just decide on your own. Well, you can,
but you ain't going to be married very
long.
>> You can't just decide on your own. You
What do you do? You always consult with
your covenant partner.
You just you consult with your covenant
partner and you're like, "Yeah, I'd like
to go. You want to go out and eat here?
You want to go eat there?" "Nah, I don't
really know what I want to eat." Well,
you know what that's code for. She's got
somewhere she wants, but she's just
waiting for you to say it. So, you got
to go down the list, right? Down the
list, down, down, down. And then we come
into agreement, right?
You don't do things without your
covenant partner. How many Christians
are functioning without their covenant
partner? Yeah,
>> they're they're functioning outside of
their covenant as if they don't even
have one. It's like slapping God in the
face.
>> And then when God said, "Here's my
promise in the word," we say, "Well, I
don't know. I don't know about that,
pastor." Boy, I don't know about that. I
don't know. It's just so hard to trust
God. Do you understand what a covenant
is? Do you understand that if God broke
his covenant, which he will not, he
said, "My covenant I will not break."
But if he did, the whole universe would
be destroyed. Because the whole
universe, the Bible says in Colossians
1, is being held together by his word.
>> He will not break his covenant. His
promises are yes
>> and so be it in my life.
>> That's covenant language.
>> Abram day after day after day had to
remind people, had to tell people, "No,
no, no, no. Abraham,
Abraham, he had a choice. He could have
succumbed and said, "Hey, hey, Abram,
come over here." I can just see him.
Act like I didn't hear him. I don't even
hear that.
That's like when you you yell, "Bill,
come here." I'm not coming. That's not
my name.
Abram's not responding to that name. He
only responds to Abraham.
I'm talking about how you can live in
your covenant.
>> We can follow the father of our faith,
Abraham.
So Abraham did not respond to Abram any
longer. Why are you responding
to those things? Why are you just
accepting those things? That's not who
you are anymore.
>> You've been given a name. The name above
every other name. That the name of
Jesus, every knee has to bow.
>> I'm in I'm in Christ. I have a covenant
with almighty God. How did I get in my
covenant? because he shed his blood
>> and he entered into the holy of holies
we talked about last week in heaven in
the temple and offered his own blood
washed my sin away. Ah you old dirty
rotten sinner I'm not a sinner.
>> Say hey sinner come here I'm not coming
either.
Do you know your covenant? Do you know
what belongs to you in your covenant? Do
you know how to live in your covenant?
Do you know the name that you've been
given?
He changed your name, too. You are now
baptized into Christ and you've been
given a name. I want us to end the
service a little bit different today. I
want us to do something a little bit
different because what I really have was
impressed by the spirit to do today
is I want us to focus on that name.
I want us to meditate
on that name.
We're going to sing a song together. I
want everyone to stand with us. Go ahead
and stand. We're going to sing a song
together. And at the end of this song,
we're going to make some declarations
in the name of Jesus. Amen.
>> Amen.
I could sing in your name [singing]
[music] for all my life and still
find [music and singing] what to love
these times.
Just [music] be the name ever on
[singing] my lips.
[music]
Sweeter every time that I call on it.
There's just something about your name.
[music and singing]
There's just something about your name
[singing]
that makes me [music] cry. Holding.
There is no other [singing] name.
There is no other name. [singing]
There is no other name. [music]
Jesus, you're worthy. [singing]
And you have been
the [music] friend
to [singing] never
left.
I won't [music]
forget
your faithfulness. [singing]
Jesus be the name [music and singing]
ever on my lips.
[music]
Sweeter every [singing] time that I call
on it. There's just something [music]
about your name.
There's just something about your name.
[singing]
>> [music]
>> There's just something about your name
that makes [music and singing] me cry
holy.
Oh, there is no other name.
There is no [singing and music] other
name.
There is no other name.
Jesus, [music]
you're [singing] worthy. Something
there's just something about your name.
There's something about
[music and singing] your name.
There's just something about your name
makes me cry [music and singing] holy.
There is no other name.
There is no [music and singing] other
name.
There is no other name.
Jesus, you're worthy. [music]
You are.
[singing]
Come on. [music] We lift up the name of
Jesus.
The name above every [singing] other
name.
[music] Oh, we thank you Lord for power
[singing] in your name.
Oh Jesus, [music and singing]
your name is like the northern light.
The one the darkness [music and singing]
can't deny. The resurrection
and the life. [singing] Jesus. [music]
Jesus. Your name can save. Your name can
heal. Your name can make [singing] the
storm be [music] still. You never fail.
We never will. Jesus.
[music and singing]
Jesus. The bread of life broken for us.
The wounded [singing] and the worthy
[music]
one. The first, the last is still
[singing] to come. Jesus. [music]
Jesus the king. The world overwhelmed
[singing]
the great. The Lord who [music] will
forever reign. The name [singing] above
all other names. Jesus. [music]
[singing] Oh Jesus be the name.
Jesus be the name.
Oh Jesus be [music] the name [singing]
that gives all the glory.
Oh Jesus [music] be the name.
Oh Jesus be the name. [music]
Jesus be the name
that gets all the [singing] glory.
[music] Oh Jesus be the name.
Jesus be the name [singing]
of it all. Jesus be [music] the name
that gets all the [singing] glory.
[music]
Oh Jesus be the name.
Jesus be [music] the name. be the name.
Jesus be the name
that can all thy [music and singing]
glory.
Oh,
[music]
[singing] Jesus
glory.
Oh, [music]
the name Jesus.
[music and singing] Jesus be the name.
Jesus be the name.
Oh [music] Jesus be the name
that gets all [singing] the glory of the
glory.
Jesus be the name. [music and singing]
Be the name. Be the name. Jesus be the
name the name be the name. [singing]
>> Jesus be the name
that gets all [music] the glory.
Oh, [music]
say the name Jesus. [music]
Oh,
[music]
[singing]
shout the name
Jesus. [music]
[singing]
Come on, lift up the name of Jesus.
[music]
>> Thank you, Lord.
>> Thank you, Jesus.
>> The name that's above all names. that at
the name of Jesus,
every knee must bow.
Cancer must bow, depression must bow,
poverty must bow,
>> viruses must bow at the name of Jesus.
>> Thank you, Jesus.
>> Oh, thank you, Lord.
>> You get all the glory
>> and praise.
Thank you, Lord.
Thank you, Jesus. Now, this is what I
want us to do.
Every single person here, you're dealing
with something.
Maybe it is sickness. Maybe it is a
virus. Maybe it's poverty. Maybe it's
been on you for your whole life.
Maybe it's anxiety or fear or
depression. Here's what I want you to
do. What we're going to do is we're
going to make a confession of faith
>> based on the word of God and our
covenant promises and we are going to
declare that whatever that is be gone
>> in the name.
Oh, I said in the name.
In the name above every name. Do you
believe that? Do you believe that his
name is above every other name?
>> Do you believe that in his name is
power,
>> authority?
Dominion.
Do you believe you have it?
>> All right, let's do it. I'm going
everybody do this together.
I'm going to say one, two, three, and
then you declare what that is. You just
speak it with your mouth. If it's
anxiety, say anxiety. If it's fear, say
fear. If it's some sort of sickness, you
say it. Heart disease, you say it.
Diabetes, you say it. Why? Because I'm
talking to it.
Do you know that Jesus talked to stuff
that most people wouldn't talk to? He
talked to a tree. He talked to sickness
and disease.
I don't know if that anxiety can hear.
Oh, you better believe it can. I don't
know if that cancer can hear. Oh, you
better believe it can.
So, we're going to do that. We're going
to we're going to speak that. And I want
you to say what it is. And the Bible
says when you believe it in your heart,
you confess that with your mouth. What
we're going to confess
is that that thing be gone in the name
of Jesus. All right, y'all ready? One,
two, three. Say it. Say it.
be gone
from my life
in the name above every name. The name
of Jesus.
Thank you Lord.
>> Thank you Lord.
>> Oh thank you Lord for our covenant
promise our covenant name.
Oh thank you Jesus.
>> Oh let's praise him for it now. All
that's left is to praise it. That's all
that's left. The work has been done. We
don't have to strive or worry or fret.
It's over.
>> Oh, thank you, Lord.
You say, "Pastor, does that mean it's a
ceasefire?" No. I'm declaring it's over.
>> The attack is over.
It's done. It's dead. It's been wiped
out.
You know, that's what the enemy has to
be. You got to deal with the enemy.
There is no negotiation with the devil.
There's no negotiation with cancer, with
anxiety or fear. Well, I'm just learning
to cope. Pastor, you need to eradicate
that from your life.
>> You need to be just like April.
Not this guy. Not anymore. I'm a
covenant man.
>> I have a covenant with God. I'm Abraham.
I'm Abraham. I don't care what I used to
be. And he said, now listen to me now.
He said it before he had the promised
child.
He said it before he had it. That's what
faith does.
Faith declares the end from the
beginning.
That's what we just did.
We just used our new covenant name, the
name above every other name. Amen.
>> That at the name of Jesus, every knee
has to bow.
Live your life
in your covenant.
Use your new name.
Don't act like a a person without a
covenant. Don't act like you're a
stranger to the covenant. It's a
promise.
Know your covenant.
You read the word of God. You see that
promise. You're like,
you know what I mean by that? That's me.
He just said it. He just gave it. That's
a promise. It's mine.
That's not who I am anymore. I'm not a
fearful person any longer. Stop saying
it. That's be like Abraham saying, "I'm
not the father of many. I'm not the
father of many. I'm not the father of
many." He didn't say that. He said, "I'm
the father of many." It's who I am now.
I got a covenant name. You have a
covenant name. You got your name
changed, too. You are baptized into
Christ. You're in covenant with God.
Amen. Father, in the name of Jesus, oh,
the name above every other name. Thank
you, Lord, for our covenant.
Thank you, Lord, that we are redeemed.
Our freedom has been purchased and we no
longer have to live as people without a
covenant with you. We can live in our
covenant. Thank you, Lord, for what
you've done 2,000 years ago. Not even
what this morning, but the work was done
2,000 years ago. I thank you, Lord, for
the revelation today that we got on what
you've already done.
the revelation on our new name. And I
thank you, Lord, that we will be a
people from this moment on who will not
be considering ourselves as people
without a covenant, but we'll walk in
our new covenant and use our new name in
the name of Jesus. Amen. Amen. Praise
God. Well, if you guys need prayer, we
got a prayer team up here. Go in the
power and authority in the name of
Jesus. You're dismissed. God bless you.
[singing]
[music]
>> Darkness can't [music] deny the
resurrection
and [singing] the life. Jesus.
Jesus. [music] Your name can save. Your
name can heal. Your name
[music and singing] can make the stor.
You never fail. You never will. Jesus,
Jesus, [music] the bread of life
[singing] broken for us. The wounded and
the worthy [music] one. The first,
[singing] the last, and still to come.
Jesus.
Jesus. [singing] The king who
overwhelmed [music] the crane. The Lord
who will forever. [singing]
The name above all other [music] names.
Jesus.
Jesus be [singing] the name. [music]
Jesus be the name.
Jesus [music] be the [singing] name
that gets all the glory.
[music] Jesus be [singing] the name.
Jesus be the [music] name.
Jesus [singing] be the name
that gets all the glory. [music]
Jesus be the name.
[music and singing] Jesus be the name
that gets all the glor.
Jesus be the [music] name.
Jesus be the name.
Jesus be the name
that gets [music and singing] all the
glory.
[singing]
Oh
[music]
Jesus.
[singing]
Oh
Jesus.
Oh we thank you Lord.
[singing]
>> We love your name.
>> Oh we bless we bless your name.
In the name of Jesus.